{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a dog or owns a snake or owns a zebra or owns a cat.", "Any person either is in green clothes or is in blue clothes or is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in pink clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Theodora, George, Peter, Ivan, Elena.", "George owns a dog.", "Peter isn't the person who is in yellow clothes.", "Theodora lives next door from Elena.", "The person who is at house 5 is not the person who owns a dog.", "The person who is in yellow clothes also owns a zebra.", "The person who is at house 4 also is in green clothes.", "Theodora is in green clothes.", "The person who is owns a snake lives next door from the one who is owns a zebra.", "Theodora lives next door from George.", "Elena isn't the person who owns a zebra."], "question": "What pet does Peter own?", "answer_options": ["owns a hamster", "owns a dog", "owns a snake", "owns a zebra", "owns a cat"], "answer": "owns a snake", "seed": 1729292803522}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a snake or owns a zebra or owns a cat or owns a dog.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in green clothes or is in red clothes or is in pink clothes or is in yellow clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Theodora, George, Peter, Elena, Ivan.", "The person who is owns a snake lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a zebra.", "George is in green clothes.", "Elena isn't the person who is in red clothes.", "Ivan isn't the person who is in red clothes.", "Elena isn't the person who is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is at house 4 also owns a snake.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who is in red clothes.", "George lives next door from Elena.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who owns a dog.", "George isn't the person who is at house 2.", "Theodora is in blue clothes.", "The person who is in pink clothes is not the person who owns a zebra.", "Peter lives next door from Ivan.", "The person who is at house 1 also owns a dog."], "question": "Which is the house of Peter?", "answer_options": ["is at house 3", "is at house 4", "is at house 2", "is at house 5", "is at house 1"], "answer": "is at house 2", "seed": 1729292805809}
{"facts": ["Any person either is in red clothes or is in pink clothes or is in green clothes or is in blue clothes or is in yellow clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Elena, George, Ivan, Peter, Theodora.", "The person who is at house 5 is not the person who is the criminal.", "Elena is at house 1.", "Peter is at house 2.", "The person who is is in pink clothes lives next door from the one who is is in green clothes.", "Theodora is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is the criminal.", "George is at house 5.", "The person who is in yellow clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "George is in pink clothes."], "question": "Who is the criminal?", "answer_options": ["Elena", "George", "Ivan", "Peter", "Theodora"], "answer": "Peter", "seed": 1729292807386}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a zebra or owns a dog or owns a cat or owns a snake.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in blue clothes or is in pink clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Elena, Ivan, George, Theodora, Peter.", "The person who is the criminal is not the person who owns a hamster.", "Theodora is the criminal.", "Peter is in green clothes.", "Ivan lives next door from George.", "The person who is in pink clothes also owns a dog.", "Ivan isn't the person who is in red clothes.", "Ivan lives next door from Peter.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is owns a zebra lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a cat.", "George lives next door from Theodora.", "The person who is owns a dog lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a snake.", "Peter owns a snake."], "question": "What pet does the person who is in red clothes own?", "answer_options": ["owns a hamster", "owns a zebra", "owns a dog", "owns a cat", "owns a snake"], "answer": "owns a hamster", "seed": 1729292810156}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a zebra or owns a dog or owns a snake or owns a cat.", "Any person either is in pink clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in green clothes or is in blue clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Ivan, George, Peter, Theodora, Elena.", "Ivan lives next door from Theodora.", "George owns a zebra.", "The person who is owns a zebra lives next door from the one who is owns a dog.", "The person who is at house 5 also is in yellow clothes.", "Elena is in red clothes.", "Peter owns a dog.", "The person who is owns a dog lives next door from the one who is owns a snake.", "The person who is in blue clothes also owns a snake."], "question": "Who is at house 1?", "answer_options": ["Ivan", "George", "Peter", "Theodora", "Elena"], "answer": "Elena", "seed": 1729292814249}
{"facts": ["Any person either is in yellow clothes or is in blue clothes or is in green clothes or is in red clothes or is in pink clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Peter, Theodora, Elena, George, Ivan.", "George is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 1 also is in pink clothes.", "The person who is at house 3 also is in blue clothes.", "The person who is in red clothes also is the criminal.", "The person who is is in yellow clothes lives next door from the one who is is in green clothes."], "question": "Who is at house 2?", "answer_options": ["Peter", "Theodora", "Elena", "George", "Ivan"], "answer": "George", "seed": 1729292816922}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a cat or owns a dog or owns a snake or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in pink clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in green clothes or is in blue clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Theodora, George, Ivan, Peter, Elena.", "Peter owns a snake.", "Theodora isn't the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who is in green clothes.", "The person who is at house 2 also owns a dog.", "Ivan isn't the person who owns a hamster.", "Theodora lives 2 doors away from Elena.", "The person who is owns a zebra lives next door from the one who is owns a snake.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who is in yellow clothes.", "George isn't the person who is at house 1.", "Theodora isn't the person who is in red clothes.", "Peter is in blue clothes."], "question": "Who is in pink clothes?", "answer_options": ["Theodora", "George", "Ivan", "Peter", "Elena"], "answer": "Theodora", "seed": 1729292818235}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a dog or owns a cat or owns a snake or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in red clothes or is in green clothes or is in pink clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Peter, Ivan, Theodora, Elena, George.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who is the criminal.", "Elena isn't the person who is the criminal.", "Theodora isn't the person who is the criminal.", "George owns a hamster.", "Elena isn't the person who owns a dog.", "Peter lives next door from Elena.", "Peter isn't the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 1 also owns a snake.", "Elena isn't the person who is in blue clothes.", "The person who is owns a dog lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a snake.", "Elena isn't the person who is at house 4.", "The person who is at house 2 also is in blue clothes.", "Theodora isn't the person who is at house 3."], "question": "What pet does the person who is the criminal own?", "answer_options": ["owns a zebra", "owns a dog", "owns a cat", "owns a snake", "owns a hamster"], "answer": "owns a hamster", "seed": 1729292830082}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a hamster or owns a cat or owns a dog or owns a snake.", "Any person either is in yellow clothes or is in red clothes or is in pink clothes or is in blue clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Theodora, Ivan, Peter, George, Elena.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is owns a hamster lives next door from the one who is owns a snake.", "Theodora isn't the person who is at house 3.", "Theodora isn't the person who is in red clothes.", "The person who is is in yellow clothes lives next door from the one who is is in green clothes.", "The person who is at house 1 also owns a dog.", "Theodora isn't the person who is in blue clothes.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who owns a zebra.", "Peter isn't the person who owns a dog.", "The person who is in pink clothes also owns a cat.", "Elena is in green clothes.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who owns a zebra.", "Peter isn't the person who owns a snake.", "Elena isn't the person who is at house 3.", "Peter isn't the person who owns a hamster."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who is at house 2?", "answer_options": ["is in yellow clothes", "is in red clothes", "is in pink clothes", "is in blue clothes", "is in green clothes"], "answer": "is in pink clothes", "seed": 1729292838110}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a zebra or owns a snake or owns a dog or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in pink clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in red clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Peter, George, Elena, Ivan, Theodora.", "The person who is at house 5 also owns a zebra.", "George is in pink clothes.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who is in red clothes.", "The person who is owns a cat lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a zebra.", "The person who is in yellow clothes is not the person who owns a dog.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who is in yellow clothes.", "Elena is at house 2.", "The person who is is in yellow clothes lives next door from the one who is is in red clothes.", "The person who is owns a cat lives next door from the one who is owns a hamster.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is owns a cat lives next door from the one who is owns a snake.", "The person who is in green clothes is not the person who owns a snake.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who is in blue clothes."], "question": "What pet does the person who is in red clothes own?", "answer_options": ["owns a cat", "owns a zebra", "owns a snake", "owns a dog", "owns a hamster"], "answer": "owns a dog", "seed": 1729292842347}
{"facts": ["Any person either is in green clothes or is in pink clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in blue clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Theodora, Ivan, Elena, Peter, George.", "Theodora is at house 2.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who is in green clothes.", "The person who is is in green clothes lives 2 doors away from the one who is is in blue clothes.", "Theodora lives 2 doors away from Peter.", "The person who is at house 3 also is in yellow clothes."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of Peter?", "answer_options": ["is in green clothes", "is in pink clothes", "is in yellow clothes", "is in blue clothes", "is in red clothes"], "answer": "is in blue clothes", "seed": 1729293603613}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a hamster or owns a dog or owns a snake or owns a cat.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in blue clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in pink clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Theodora, Peter, Elena, George, Ivan.", "The person who is owns a zebra lives next door from the one who is owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 5 also owns a snake.", "Peter is the criminal.", "The person who is in blue clothes also owns a hamster.", "Elena isn't the person who owns a cat.", "Elena lives 2 doors away from George.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is is in red clothes lives next door from the one who is is in green clothes.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "George is at house 5.", "George is in pink clothes.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who is in green clothes.", "Elena isn't the person who owns a zebra."], "question": "Who is at house 4?", "answer_options": ["Theodora", "Peter", "Elena", "George", "Ivan"], "answer": "Peter", "seed": 1729293606678}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a snake or owns a zebra or owns a dog or owns a cat or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in red clothes or is in green clothes or is in pink clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Theodora, Ivan, Peter, George, Elena.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 5 is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is in yellow clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who owns a snake.", "Ivan owns a zebra.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is is in blue clothes lives 2 doors away from the one who is is in green clothes.", "The person who is at house 1 also is in red clothes.", "The person who is at house 2 also is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is owns a cat lives next door from the one who is owns a hamster.", "George is in green clothes.", "Ivan is at house 2.", "Theodora is at house 3."], "question": "What pet does the person who is the criminal own?", "answer_options": ["owns a snake", "owns a zebra", "owns a dog", "owns a cat", "owns a hamster"], "answer": "owns a dog", "seed": 1729293611558}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a zebra or owns a dog or owns a hamster or owns a snake.", "Any person either is in green clothes or is in red clothes or is in blue clothes or is in pink clothes or is in yellow clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Theodora, Peter, Elena, George, Ivan.", "The person who is in green clothes also owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 2 also owns a zebra.", "Theodora owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 5 is not the person who is in yellow clothes.", "Elena lives next door from George.", "The person who is is in green clothes lives 2 doors away from the one who is is in yellow clothes.", "Peter owns a zebra.", "The person who is at house 3 also owns a cat."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of Ivan?", "answer_options": ["is in green clothes", "is in red clothes", "is in blue clothes", "is in pink clothes", "is in yellow clothes"], "answer": "is in yellow clothes", "seed": 1729293623171}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a dog or owns a hamster or owns a zebra or owns a cat or owns a snake.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in red clothes or is in pink clothes or is in green clothes or is in yellow clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Theodora, Elena, Peter, George, Ivan.", "George is at house 3.", "The person who is owns a dog lives next door from the one who is owns a zebra.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is is in pink clothes lives 2 doors away from the one who is is in green clothes.", "Theodora isn't the person who is at house 1.", "Theodora isn't the person who is at house 4.", "Ivan isn't the person who is at house 1.", "The person who is in green clothes also owns a cat.", "Ivan isn't the person who owns a hamster.", "Theodora owns a dog.", "Theodora is in blue clothes.", "The person who is at house 5 is not the person who owns a cat."], "question": "Who owns a snake?", "answer_options": ["Theodora", "Elena", "Peter", "George", "Ivan"], "answer": "Ivan", "seed": 1729293626617}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a dog or owns a zebra or owns a hamster or owns a snake or owns a cat.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in red clothes or is in pink clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are George, Theodora, Elena, Ivan, Peter.", "Elena isn't the person who owns a snake.", "The person who is in yellow clothes also owns a zebra.", "The person who is is in yellow clothes lives next door from the one who is is in red clothes.", "The person who is at house 2 also is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 1 also owns a dog.", "Elena lives 2 doors away from Peter.", "Peter isn't the person who is in red clothes.", "The person who is the criminal also owns a cat.", "Peter is the criminal.", "Elena isn't the person who is in yellow clothes."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who owns a hamster?", "answer_options": ["is in blue clothes", "is in yellow clothes", "is in red clothes", "is in pink clothes", "is in green clothes"], "answer": "is in red clothes", "seed": 1729293632720}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a snake or owns a cat or owns a dog or owns a hamster or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in pink clothes or is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in blue clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "The person who is the criminal also owns a cat.", "The person who is in red clothes also is the criminal.", "The person who is is in pink clothes lives next door from the one who is is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is is in blue clothes lives next door from the one who is is in green clothes.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who is in red clothes.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who owns a cat."], "question": "What pet does the person who is at house 5 own?", "answer_options": ["owns a snake", "owns a cat", "owns a dog", "owns a hamster", "owns a zebra"], "answer": "owns a cat", "seed": 1729293636403}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a dog or owns a hamster or owns a cat or owns a snake or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in pink clothes or is in blue clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "The person who is at house 3 also is in pink clothes.", "The person who is in red clothes also owns a dog.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who owns a snake.", "The person who is at house 1 also owns a dog.", "The person who is at house 4 also owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who owns a snake.", "The person who is in green clothes also owns a zebra."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who is at house 5?", "answer_options": ["is in red clothes", "is in pink clothes", "is in blue clothes", "is in yellow clothes", "is in green clothes"], "answer": "is in yellow clothes", "seed": 1729293641279}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a dog or owns a cat or owns a hamster or owns a snake or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in green clothes or is in pink clothes or is in red clothes or is in blue clothes or is in yellow clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Peter, Ivan, Elena, George, Theodora.", "George isn't the person who owns a cat.", "The person who is owns a dog lives next door from the one who is owns a zebra.", "Elena lives next door from George.", "Elena owns a hamster.", "Theodora isn't the person who is in pink clothes.", "Theodora isn't the person who owns a dog.", "The person who is in yellow clothes is not the person who owns a snake.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who owns a dog.", "The person who is in pink clothes also owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who is in green clothes.", "George isn't the person who is in red clothes.", "Elena isn't the person who is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is in yellow clothes is not the person who owns a dog.", "The person who is owns a dog lives next door from the one who is owns a snake.", "George isn't the person who owns a zebra.", "Peter isn't the person who is at house 5.", "The person who is at house 4 also is in red clothes."], "question": "Who is in green clothes?", "answer_options": ["Peter", "Ivan", "Elena", "George", "Theodora"], "answer": "Peter", "seed": 1729293644532}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a hamster or owns a dog or owns a cat or owns a snake.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Ivan, Theodora, George, Peter, Elena.", "The person who is owns a dog lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a snake.", "Elena is at house 1.", "George lives 2 doors away from Peter.", "Peter isn't the person who is at house 3.", "Elena owns a snake.", "Theodora lives next door from Elena."], "question": "What pet does George own?", "answer_options": ["owns a zebra", "owns a hamster", "owns a dog", "owns a cat", "owns a snake"], "answer": "owns a dog", "seed": 1729293650893}
{"facts": ["Any person either is in green clothes or is in pink clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in blue clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Ivan, Elena, George, Peter, Theodora.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who is in green clothes.", "The person who is is in pink clothes lives next door from the one who is is in red clothes.", "George is in yellow clothes.", "George is at house 3.", "The person who is is in green clothes lives next door from the one who is is in yellow clothes."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who is at house 5?", "answer_options": ["is in green clothes", "is in pink clothes", "is in yellow clothes", "is in blue clothes", "is in red clothes"], "answer": "is in blue clothes", "seed": 1729293652703}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a dog or owns a snake or owns a hamster or owns a cat.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in pink clothes or is in blue clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Ivan, George, Peter, Theodora, Elena.", "George is at house 4.", "The person who is at house 5 is not the person who owns a dog.", "The person who is at house 5 also is in green clothes.", "The person who is in blue clothes also owns a snake.", "Elena is at house 5.", "The person who is at house 2 also owns a hamster.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who is in pink clothes.", "The person who is in pink clothes is not the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who is in pink clothes.", "Elena isn't the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is owns a dog lives next door from the one who is owns a snake."], "question": "Who owns a dog?", "answer_options": ["Ivan", "George", "Peter", "Theodora", "Elena"], "answer": "George", "seed": 1729293655320}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a dog or owns a snake or owns a hamster or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in pink clothes or is in green clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in blue clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "The person who is the criminal also owns a hamster.", "The person who is at house 3 also is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is in blue clothes also is the criminal.", "The person who is is in pink clothes lives 2 doors away from the one who is is in green clothes.", "The person who is is in pink clothes lives next door from the one who is is in red clothes.", "The person who is at house 5 also owns a hamster."], "question": "Which is the house of the person who is in pink clothes?", "answer_options": ["is at house 2", "is at house 4", "is at house 3", "is at house 5", "is at house 1"], "answer": "is at house 2", "seed": 1729293658511}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a hamster or owns a cat or owns a dog or owns a snake.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in green clothes or is in pink clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Ivan, Peter, George, Theodora, Elena.", "Theodora owns a dog.", "The person who is at house 3 also is in pink clothes.", "Ivan is at house 5.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who owns a dog.", "George is in pink clothes.", "Ivan lives next door from Peter."], "question": "Who is at house 2?", "answer_options": ["Ivan", "Peter", "George", "Theodora", "Elena"], "answer": "Elena", "seed": 1729293660229}
{"facts": ["Any person either is in yellow clothes or is in red clothes or is in green clothes or is in pink clothes or is in blue clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "People's names are George, Ivan, Theodora, Elena, Peter.", "Theodora lives next door from Elena.", "Ivan lives next door from Theodora.", "The person who is at house 3 also is in green clothes.", "Ivan is at house 2.", "George isn't the person who is in red clothes.", "George isn't the person who is in blue clothes.", "The person who is at house 4 also is in pink clothes."], "question": "Who is in yellow clothes?", "answer_options": ["George", "Ivan", "Theodora", "Elena", "Peter"], "answer": "George", "seed": 1729293663231}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a snake or owns a dog or owns a hamster or owns a cat.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in pink clothes or is in blue clothes or is in green clothes or is in yellow clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Ivan, Theodora, Peter, Elena, George.", "The person who is the criminal is not the person who owns a zebra.", "Peter is at house 1.", "The person who is the criminal is not the person who owns a dog.", "The person who is is in blue clothes lives next door from the one who is is in green clothes.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 5 is not the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is in yellow clothes also owns a cat.", "The person who is owns a hamster lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a cat.", "The person who is the criminal is not the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is in red clothes also owns a zebra.", "Ivan is in red clothes.", "The person who is at house 4 also is in yellow clothes.", "Peter isn't the person who owns a snake."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who is the criminal?", "answer_options": ["is in red clothes", "is in pink clothes", "is in blue clothes", "is in green clothes", "is in yellow clothes"], "answer": "is in pink clothes", "seed": 1729293667898}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a snake or owns a zebra or owns a hamster or owns a cat or owns a dog.", "Any person either is in yellow clothes or is in pink clothes or is in green clothes or is in red clothes or is in blue clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Theodora, Ivan, George, Peter, Elena.", "George isn't the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is the criminal is not the person who owns a zebra.", "Theodora isn't the person who is the criminal.", "Peter isn't the person who is the criminal.", "George lives next door from Peter.", "George isn't the person who is in yellow clothes.", "Peter isn't the person who is in yellow clothes.", "Elena isn't the person who is in green clothes.", "Ivan owns a zebra.", "The person who is at house 5 is not the person who is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who is in pink clothes.", "The person who is at house 4 also is in red clothes.", "The person who is is in yellow clothes lives next door from the one who is is in red clothes.", "Elena isn't the person who is in yellow clothes.", "Ivan is at house 1."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who is the criminal?", "answer_options": ["is in yellow clothes", "is in pink clothes", "is in green clothes", "is in red clothes", "is in blue clothes"], "answer": "is in blue clothes", "seed": 1729293672823}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a snake or owns a dog or owns a cat or owns a zebra or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in green clothes or is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in blue clothes or is in pink clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "People's names are George, Elena, Ivan, Peter, Theodora.", "Theodora owns a hamster.", "The person who is owns a zebra lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a hamster.", "Theodora is at house 5.", "Ivan is in yellow clothes.", "Elena owns a dog.", "The person who is at house 5 is not the person who is in blue clothes.", "The person who is at house 4 also is in green clothes.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who owns a dog.", "The person who is is in green clothes lives next door from the one who is is in blue clothes.", "The person who is in green clothes is not the person who owns a cat."], "question": "Who owns a cat?", "answer_options": ["George", "Elena", "Ivan", "Peter", "Theodora"], "answer": "Ivan", "seed": 1729293677656}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a dog or owns a hamster or owns a cat or owns a snake or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in pink clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in red clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Ivan, Elena, George, Theodora, Peter.", "The person who is in green clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is the criminal is not the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is the criminal.", "Theodora isn't the person who is in green clothes.", "The person who is is in blue clothes lives next door from the one who is is in green clothes.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who owns a dog.", "Theodora owns a snake.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 3 also owns a zebra.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who is in green clothes.", "Elena owns a hamster.", "Theodora lives 2 doors away from Peter.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who is in blue clothes.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who owns a snake.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "Ivan is at house 4.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who owns a hamster.", "Elena isn't the person who is in blue clothes."], "question": "Who is the criminal?", "answer_options": ["Ivan", "Elena", "George", "Theodora", "Peter"], "answer": "Theodora", "seed": 1729293680065}
{"facts": ["Any person either is in blue clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in red clothes or is in pink clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "The person who is at house 3 also is in red clothes.", "The person who is at house 1 also is in green clothes.", "The person who is is in blue clothes lives next door from the one who is is in pink clothes.", "The person who is is in blue clothes lives 2 doors away from the one who is is in yellow clothes."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who is at house 4?", "answer_options": ["is in blue clothes", "is in yellow clothes", "is in red clothes", "is in pink clothes", "is in green clothes"], "answer": "is in blue clothes", "seed": 1729293684332}
{"facts": ["Any person either is in pink clothes or is in red clothes or is in green clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in blue clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "The person who is in yellow clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is in pink clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 3 also is in blue clothes.", "The person who is in green clothes is not the person who is the criminal."], "question": "Which is the house of the person who is the criminal?", "answer_options": ["is at house 1", "is at house 4", "is at house 2", "is at house 5", "is at house 3"], "answer": "is at house 3", "seed": 1729293686078}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a snake or owns a zebra or owns a dog or owns a hamster or owns a cat.", "Any person either is in yellow clothes or is in green clothes or is in pink clothes or is in blue clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Peter, Theodora, Ivan, George, Elena.", "Ivan is at house 5.", "Theodora isn't the person who owns a cat.", "Peter isn't the person who is in green clothes.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who owns a snake.", "The person who is is in green clothes lives next door from the one who is is in red clothes.", "The person who is in pink clothes is not the person who owns a snake.", "The person who is in red clothes also owns a cat.", "The person who is owns a zebra lives next door from the one who is owns a hamster.", "Peter lives next door from George.", "Peter isn't the person who is in red clothes.", "The person who is at house 3 also owns a hamster.", "The person who is at house 5 also is in pink clothes.", "Theodora isn't the person who is at house 4."], "question": "Who is at house 2?", "answer_options": ["Peter", "Theodora", "Ivan", "George", "Elena"], "answer": "Theodora", "seed": 1729293689536}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a snake or owns a hamster or owns a dog or owns a zebra or owns a cat.", "Any person either is in pink clothes or is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in blue clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "The person who is is in pink clothes lives next door from the one who is is in blue clothes.", "The person who is at house 4 also is in blue clothes.", "The person who is at house 2 also owns a dog.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who owns a dog.", "The person who is at house 1 also is in green clothes."], "question": "What pet does the person who is in yellow clothes own?", "answer_options": ["owns a snake", "owns a hamster", "owns a dog", "owns a zebra", "owns a cat"], "answer": "owns a dog", "seed": 1729293694187}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a dog or owns a zebra or owns a cat or owns a snake or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in yellow clothes or is in green clothes or is in red clothes or is in pink clothes or is in blue clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Elena, Peter, Ivan, Theodora, George.", "Peter isn't the person who is at house 5.", "Ivan is in red clothes.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who is in pink clothes.", "The person who is is in red clothes lives next door from the one who is is in pink clothes.", "Theodora isn't the person who is in green clothes.", "The person who is at house 5 is not the person who is in pink clothes.", "The person who is at house 5 is not the person who is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is at house 5 is not the person who owns a dog.", "Theodora isn't the person who is in blue clothes.", "Elena owns a dog."], "question": "Which is the house of George?", "answer_options": ["is at house 1", "is at house 4", "is at house 2", "is at house 3", "is at house 5"], "answer": "is at house 5", "seed": 1729293696467}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a hamster or owns a zebra or owns a snake or owns a dog.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in pink clothes or is in green clothes.", "People's names are Elena, George, Ivan, Peter, Theodora.", "The person who is in red clothes also owns a hamster.", "Ivan isn't the person who owns a cat.", "Peter owns a snake.", "Ivan isn't the person who is in red clothes.", "Theodora owns a dog."], "question": "Who owns a zebra?", "answer_options": ["Elena", "George", "Ivan", "Peter", "Theodora"], "answer": "Ivan", "seed": 1729293699739}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a dog or owns a snake or owns a cat or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in pink clothes or is in blue clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in red clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Elena, Theodora, George, Ivan, Peter.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is in pink clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is in green clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "Elena lives 2 doors away from Ivan.", "Theodora isn't the person who is in red clothes.", "Theodora isn't the person who owns a snake.", "The person who is is in blue clothes lives 2 doors away from the one who is is in red clothes.", "The person who is at house 1 also owns a dog.", "The person who is at house 5 also is in pink clothes.", "The person who is owns a zebra lives next door from the one who is owns a hamster.", "Theodora lives next door from George.", "The person who is at house 3 also owns a cat.", "The person who is in yellow clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "Elena is in pink clothes.", "Peter is in green clothes."], "question": "Which is the house of the person who is the criminal?", "answer_options": ["is at house 5", "is at house 1", "is at house 2", "is at house 3", "is at house 4"], "answer": "is at house 1", "seed": 1729293701068}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a snake or owns a zebra or owns a hamster or owns a cat or owns a dog.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in pink clothes or is in red clothes or is in green clothes or is in yellow clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Theodora, George, Elena, Peter, Ivan.", "The person who is at house 5 is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is is in pink clothes lives 2 doors away from the one who is is in red clothes.", "George lives next door from Ivan.", "George lives next door from Peter.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is in green clothes.", "The person who is in green clothes is not the person who owns a dog.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "Ivan isn't the person who is at house 1.", "Ivan isn't the person who is in green clothes.", "Theodora lives next door from Elena.", "The person who is at house 3 also owns a dog.", "The person who is in pink clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "George is in pink clothes."], "question": "Who is the criminal?", "answer_options": ["Theodora", "George", "Elena", "Peter", "Ivan"], "answer": "Ivan", "seed": 1729293706718}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a snake or owns a hamster or owns a cat or owns a zebra or owns a dog.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in green clothes or is in pink clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Ivan, Elena, Theodora, George, Peter.", "Elena lives 2 doors away from George.", "George is in green clothes.", "The person who is in green clothes is not the person who owns a dog.", "The person who is at house 5 also owns a zebra.", "Ivan is at house 4.", "George isn't the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is owns a snake lives next door from the one who is owns a zebra.", "Ivan lives 2 doors away from Peter.", "The person who is in yellow clothes also owns a cat."], "question": "Which is the house of Theodora?", "answer_options": ["is at house 4", "is at house 3", "is at house 1", "is at house 5", "is at house 2"], "answer": "is at house 1", "seed": 1729293713052}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a snake or owns a zebra or owns a hamster or owns a dog or owns a cat.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in green clothes or is in blue clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in pink clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "The person who is at house 2 also is in green clothes.", "The person who is at house 4 also owns a dog.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who is in red clothes.", "The person who is in pink clothes also owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 3 also is in blue clothes."], "question": "What pet does the person who is in yellow clothes own?", "answer_options": ["owns a snake", "owns a zebra", "owns a hamster", "owns a dog", "owns a cat"], "answer": "owns a dog", "seed": 1729293715257}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a snake or owns a hamster or owns a zebra or owns a dog or owns a cat.", "Any person either is in pink clothes or is in red clothes or is in blue clothes or is in green clothes or is in yellow clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "People's names are George, Ivan, Peter, Theodora, Elena.", "Ivan isn't the person who is in blue clothes.", "The person who is in yellow clothes also owns a cat.", "George lives 2 doors away from Theodora.", "Theodora isn't the person who is in red clothes.", "Ivan isn't the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is in pink clothes also owns a snake.", "The person who is is in green clothes lives next door from the one who is is in yellow clothes.", "Ivan is at house 4.", "George owns a snake.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is in blue clothes.", "The person who is at house 3 also owns a snake.", "The person who is at house 5 is not the person who owns a dog.", "Elena is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who owns a dog."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who owns a zebra?", "answer_options": ["is in pink clothes", "is in red clothes", "is in blue clothes", "is in green clothes", "is in yellow clothes"], "answer": "is in blue clothes", "seed": 1729293716641}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a dog or owns a zebra or owns a cat or owns a snake or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in pink clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in blue clothes or is in red clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Peter, Elena, Theodora, Ivan, George.", "The person who is in green clothes is not the person who owns a snake.", "Elena owns a zebra.", "The person who is in green clothes is not the person who owns a dog.", "Theodora lives next door from Ivan.", "The person who is at house 5 also owns a dog.", "Ivan isn't the person who is in green clothes.", "Theodora owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 1 also owns a cat.", "The person who is in green clothes is not the person who owns a zebra.", "Theodora isn't the person who is in green clothes."], "question": "Who owns a snake?", "answer_options": ["Peter", "Elena", "Theodora", "Ivan", "George"], "answer": "Ivan", "seed": 1729293718559}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a snake or owns a zebra or owns a cat or owns a dog or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in blue clothes or is in green clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in pink clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Ivan, Elena, George, Peter, Theodora.", "The person who is at house 1 also owns a dog.", "Theodora is in pink clothes.", "The person who is owns a cat lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a hamster.", "George isn't the person who is at house 4.", "Theodora isn't the person who owns a snake.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who is in pink clothes.", "The person who is owns a zebra lives next door from the one who is owns a cat.", "George owns a cat.", "Ivan lives 2 doors away from Elena.", "Theodora isn't the person who owns a dog.", "The person who is at house 3 also is in green clothes."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who is at house 5?", "answer_options": ["is in red clothes", "is in blue clothes", "is in green clothes", "is in yellow clothes", "is in pink clothes"], "answer": "is in pink clothes", "seed": 1729293721232}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a cat or owns a snake or owns a dog or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in green clothes or is in red clothes or is in pink clothes or is in blue clothes or is in yellow clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Ivan, George, Elena, Peter, Theodora.", "The person who is owns a cat lives next door from the one who is owns a snake.", "Peter lives next door from Theodora.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 4 also is in red clothes.", "Ivan lives 2 doors away from Elena.", "Ivan isn't the person who is in blue clothes.", "Theodora is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is owns a snake lives next door from the one who is owns a zebra.", "The person who is is in pink clothes lives next door from the one who is is in yellow clothes.", "Ivan isn't the person who owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 1 also owns a dog.", "Elena is in pink clothes."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who owns a hamster?", "answer_options": ["is in green clothes", "is in red clothes", "is in pink clothes", "is in blue clothes", "is in yellow clothes"], "answer": "is in green clothes", "seed": 1729293723229}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a dog or owns a cat or owns a hamster or owns a zebra or owns a snake.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in green clothes or is in blue clothes or is in pink clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Elena, Ivan, Peter, George, Theodora.", "The person who is owns a dog lives next door from the one who is owns a zebra.", "The person who is in red clothes also owns a dog.", "Ivan owns a cat.", "The person who is owns a zebra lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a snake.", "Theodora owns a snake.", "The person who is in yellow clothes is not the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is is in green clothes lives next door from the one who is is in pink clothes.", "The person who is at house 5 also owns a cat.", "Ivan lives 2 doors away from Theodora."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who is at house 1?", "answer_options": ["is in red clothes", "is in yellow clothes", "is in green clothes", "is in blue clothes", "is in pink clothes"], "answer": "is in blue clothes", "seed": 1729293727744}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a zebra or owns a cat or owns a dog or owns a snake.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in blue clothes or is in green clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in pink clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Elena, Theodora, Ivan, George, Peter.", "The person who is owns a cat lives next door from the one who is owns a dog.", "Elena isn't the person who is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is at house 2 also is in yellow clothes.", "Peter isn't the person who owns a zebra.", "Ivan is at house 1.", "The person who is is in red clothes lives 2 doors away from the one who is is in yellow clothes.", "Elena isn't the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is in red clothes also owns a hamster.", "The person who is in green clothes is not the person who owns a zebra.", "Ivan isn't the person who is in blue clothes.", "George lives next door from Peter.", "Peter is in pink clothes."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of George?", "answer_options": ["is in red clothes", "is in blue clothes", "is in green clothes", "is in yellow clothes", "is in pink clothes"], "answer": "is in yellow clothes", "seed": 1729293730764}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a dog or owns a zebra or owns a snake or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in red clothes or is in pink clothes or is in green clothes or is in yellow clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Theodora, Peter, Elena, George, Ivan.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is is in red clothes lives next door from the one who is is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who is in pink clothes.", "Peter isn't the person who owns a hamster.", "Peter is at house 4.", "Theodora is in blue clothes.", "Theodora is at house 1.", "The person who is at house 3 also owns a zebra.", "Elena is in pink clothes.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who owns a snake.", "Peter isn't the person who owns a snake.", "Theodora isn't the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is in pink clothes is not the person who owns a hamster."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who owns a snake?", "answer_options": ["is in blue clothes", "is in red clothes", "is in pink clothes", "is in green clothes", "is in yellow clothes"], "answer": "is in green clothes", "seed": 1729293732897}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a snake or owns a zebra or owns a dog or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in pink clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in blue clothes or is in green clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Elena, Peter, Ivan, George, Theodora.", "The person who is is in pink clothes lives next door from the one who is is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is is in blue clothes lives 2 doors away from the one who is is in red clothes.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who is in green clothes.", "The person who is at house 5 is not the person who is in blue clothes.", "Elena owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who owns a cat.", "The person who is in yellow clothes is not the person who owns a cat.", "The person who is in red clothes also owns a hamster.", "The person who is owns a zebra lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a hamster."], "question": "Who is in pink clothes?", "answer_options": ["Elena", "Peter", "Ivan", "George", "Theodora"], "answer": "Elena", "seed": 1729293735641}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a zebra or owns a dog or owns a cat or owns a snake.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in green clothes or is in blue clothes or is in pink clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are George, Peter, Ivan, Theodora, Elena.", "The person who is the criminal also owns a dog.", "George isn't the person who is in blue clothes.", "The person who is is in red clothes lives next door from the one who is is in blue clothes.", "Theodora isn't the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is is in red clothes lives next door from the one who is is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is is in yellow clothes lives next door from the one who is is in green clothes.", "George isn't the person who is in green clothes.", "The person who is at house 5 also is in blue clothes.", "Peter is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is at house 2 also owns a dog.", "Elena is in pink clothes."], "question": "Which is the house of Theodora?", "answer_options": ["is at house 4", "is at house 3", "is at house 2", "is at house 5", "is at house 1"], "answer": "is at house 5", "seed": 1729293738741}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a snake or owns a zebra or owns a dog or owns a cat.", "Any person either is in yellow clothes or is in green clothes or is in blue clothes or is in pink clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are George, Peter, Elena, Theodora, Ivan.", "Elena isn't the person who is the criminal.", "George isn't the person who is the criminal.", "Theodora isn't the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 3 also is in green clothes.", "Theodora owns a dog.", "The person who is owns a zebra lives next door from the one who is owns a dog.", "George owns a hamster.", "Elena owns a zebra.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is in green clothes is not the person who owns a cat.", "The person who is owns a snake lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a cat."], "question": "What pet does the person who is the criminal own?", "answer_options": ["owns a hamster", "owns a snake", "owns a zebra", "owns a dog", "owns a cat"], "answer": "owns a cat", "seed": 1729293740679}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a snake or owns a hamster or owns a dog or owns a cat or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in yellow clothes or is in pink clothes or is in green clothes or is in blue clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Elena, Theodora, George, Ivan, Peter.", "The person who is owns a hamster lives next door from the one who is owns a dog.", "Theodora lives 2 doors away from Ivan.", "Elena isn't the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is at house 5 also is in yellow clothes.", "Elena isn't the person who is at house 1.", "The person who is in yellow clothes is not the person who owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 3 also is the criminal.", "Theodora is at house 4.", "George isn't the person who owns a snake.", "Elena isn't the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who owns a snake.", "Peter isn't the person who owns a snake."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who owns a snake?", "answer_options": ["is in yellow clothes", "is in pink clothes", "is in green clothes", "is in blue clothes", "is in red clothes"], "answer": "is in yellow clothes", "seed": 1729293743930}
{"facts": ["They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "People's names are George, Peter, Ivan, Theodora, Elena.", "George lives 2 doors away from Ivan.", "Ivan is at house 2."], "question": "Who is at house 4?", "answer_options": ["George", "Peter", "Ivan", "Theodora", "Elena"], "answer": "George", "seed": 1729293747396}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a snake or owns a dog or owns a zebra or owns a hamster or owns a cat.", "Any person either is in green clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in blue clothes or is in red clothes or is in pink clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Peter, Theodora, Ivan, Elena, George.", "The person who is in green clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 3 also is in pink clothes.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is is in green clothes lives 2 doors away from the one who is is in pink clothes.", "The person who is at house 5 is not the person who owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who owns a zebra.", "George owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is owns a snake lives next door from the one who is owns a dog.", "The person who is in green clothes is not the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is the criminal is not the person who owns a cat.", "Theodora lives 2 doors away from Ivan.", "Elena is at house 1.", "Theodora is in yellow clothes.", "Peter lives next door from Theodora."], "question": "Who is the criminal?", "answer_options": ["Peter", "Theodora", "Ivan", "Elena", "George"], "answer": "Ivan", "seed": 1729293749025}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a snake or owns a cat or owns a hamster or owns a dog or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in green clothes or is in blue clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in pink clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Peter, George, Theodora, Ivan, Elena.", "The person who is at house 5 is not the person who is in blue clothes.", "The person who is at house 2 also is in red clothes.", "Theodora isn't the person who is at house 4.", "Ivan owns a dog.", "Elena isn't the person who is the criminal.", "Peter lives 2 doors away from Ivan.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who is in green clothes.", "George is in green clothes.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who is in blue clothes.", "Elena isn't the person who is at house 1.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who owns a dog.", "The person who is in pink clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 4 also is the criminal.", "Ivan isn't the person who is in blue clothes."], "question": "Who is in pink clothes?", "answer_options": ["Peter", "George", "Theodora", "Ivan", "Elena"], "answer": "Elena", "seed": 1729293754848}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a zebra or owns a cat or owns a dog or owns a snake.", "Any person either is in yellow clothes or is in red clothes or is in green clothes or is in pink clothes or is in blue clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Ivan, Theodora, George, Peter, Elena.", "Ivan isn't the person who owns a zebra.", "Peter is in pink clothes.", "The person who is at house 5 is not the person who is in green clothes.", "The person who is owns a zebra lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a dog.", "Theodora lives next door from Elena.", "George lives next door from Peter.", "The person who is at house 4 also is in blue clothes.", "Ivan isn't the person who is at house 1.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who owns a dog.", "George owns a cat.", "The person who is is in red clothes lives 2 doors away from the one who is is in pink clothes."], "question": "Who is in yellow clothes?", "answer_options": ["Ivan", "Theodora", "George", "Peter", "Elena"], "answer": "Ivan", "seed": 1729293756940}
{"facts": ["They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "People's names are George, Peter, Ivan, Theodora, Elena.", "Peter lives 2 doors away from Elena.", "Elena is at house 1."], "question": "Which is the house of Peter?", "answer_options": ["is at house 2", "is at house 3", "is at house 5", "is at house 4", "is at house 1"], "answer": "is at house 3", "seed": 1729293759742}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a dog or owns a cat or owns a hamster or owns a zebra or owns a snake.", "Any person either is in pink clothes or is in blue clothes or is in green clothes or is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Peter, George, Theodora, Ivan, Elena.", "Ivan isn't the person who owns a snake.", "The person who is at house 5 is not the person who is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is in yellow clothes is not the person who owns a cat.", "Peter owns a dog.", "The person who is at house 1 also owns a zebra.", "Ivan isn't the person who is at house 3.", "The person who is at house 5 also owns a hamster.", "George lives next door from Theodora.", "The person who is is in pink clothes lives 2 doors away from the one who is is in red clothes.", "The person who is in pink clothes also owns a dog.", "Theodora owns a hamster.", "Theodora isn't the person who is in red clothes.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who owns a snake.", "Elena isn't the person who owns a cat."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of Ivan?", "answer_options": ["is in pink clothes", "is in blue clothes", "is in green clothes", "is in red clothes", "is in yellow clothes"], "answer": "is in red clothes", "seed": 1729293761536}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a snake or owns a cat or owns a zebra or owns a hamster or owns a dog.", "Any person either is in yellow clothes or is in blue clothes or is in green clothes or is in red clothes or is in pink clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are George, Ivan, Theodora, Elena, Peter.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is in pink clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is in pink clothes is not the person who owns a snake.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is the criminal.", "Peter isn't the person who is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is at house 2 also owns a zebra.", "The person who is in red clothes also owns a hamster.", "Elena is in red clothes.", "Peter isn't the person who owns a zebra.", "Ivan isn't the person who is in green clothes.", "The person who is is in red clothes lives next door from the one who is is in pink clothes.", "George isn't the person who is in green clothes.", "Ivan isn't the person who owns a snake.", "The person who is owns a snake lives next door from the one who is owns a dog.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who owns a snake.", "Elena isn't the person who is at house 5.", "The person who is at house 2 also is in green clothes."], "question": "Who is the criminal?", "answer_options": ["George", "Ivan", "Theodora", "Elena", "Peter"], "answer": "George", "seed": 1729293763307}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a hamster or owns a zebra or owns a snake or owns a dog.", "Any person either is in pink clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in green clothes or is in blue clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Peter, George, Theodora, Ivan, Elena.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is is in yellow clothes lives next door from the one who is is in blue clothes.", "The person who is owns a cat lives next door from the one who is owns a hamster.", "Peter isn't the person who is the criminal.", "Ivan lives 2 doors away from Elena.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who owns a cat.", "The person who is in green clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "George owns a hamster.", "Peter owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 3 also is in blue clothes.", "The person who is in yellow clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is is in pink clothes lives next door from the one who is is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who is in red clothes.", "The person who is at house 5 also owns a cat."], "question": "Who is in green clothes?", "answer_options": ["Peter", "George", "Theodora", "Ivan", "Elena"], "answer": "Theodora", "seed": 1729293771298}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a dog or owns a cat or owns a hamster or owns a snake.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in green clothes or is in blue clothes or is in pink clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Ivan, Peter, George, Theodora, Elena.", "The person who is in yellow clothes also owns a dog.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is owns a dog lives next door from the one who is owns a hamster.", "George isn't the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is in yellow clothes.", "Ivan lives next door from George.", "Peter isn't the person who is in blue clothes.", "The person who is is in green clothes lives next door from the one who is is in pink clothes.", "George isn't the person who is in blue clothes.", "Elena is in pink clothes.", "The person who is at house 5 also is in blue clothes.", "Peter isn't the person who owns a hamster.", "Peter isn't the person who owns a snake.", "The person who is at house 3 also owns a snake.", "Peter isn't the person who owns a zebra."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who owns a cat?", "answer_options": ["is in red clothes", "is in yellow clothes", "is in green clothes", "is in blue clothes", "is in pink clothes"], "answer": "is in green clothes", "seed": 1729293774634}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a snake or owns a cat or owns a dog or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in blue clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in green clothes or is in pink clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Theodora, Elena, Ivan, Peter, George.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who is in pink clothes.", "The person who is at house 5 is not the person who owns a cat.", "Elena is at house 5.", "Ivan isn't the person who is at house 3.", "The person who is owns a zebra lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a snake.", "The person who is owns a zebra lives next door from the one who is owns a hamster.", "Peter owns a dog.", "Ivan isn't the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who owns a cat.", "George isn't the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is is in yellow clothes lives 2 doors away from the one who is is in pink clothes.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who is in yellow clothes.", "Theodora is in red clothes."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of George?", "answer_options": ["is in red clothes", "is in blue clothes", "is in yellow clothes", "is in green clothes", "is in pink clothes"], "answer": "is in pink clothes", "seed": 1729293778612}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a snake or owns a hamster or owns a zebra or owns a cat or owns a dog.", "Any person either is in pink clothes or is in green clothes or is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in blue clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Theodora, Ivan, Elena, Peter, George.", "Theodora is in pink clothes.", "The person who is in red clothes also owns a zebra.", "The person who is in green clothes is not the person who owns a cat.", "Elena is in red clothes.", "Peter isn't the person who is at house 2.", "Peter isn't the person who is at house 3.", "The person who is in green clothes is not the person who owns a dog.", "The person who is at house 1 also owns a dog.", "The person who is owns a hamster lives next door from the one who is owns a dog.", "The person who is owns a snake lives next door from the one who is owns a hamster.", "George isn't the person who owns a snake.", "George isn't the person who is at house 2."], "question": "Who is in green clothes?", "answer_options": ["Theodora", "Ivan", "Elena", "Peter", "George"], "answer": "Ivan", "seed": 1729293781516}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a snake or owns a hamster or owns a zebra or owns a dog or owns a cat.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in green clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in blue clothes or is in pink clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Peter, Ivan, George, Theodora, Elena.", "The person who is is in red clothes lives next door from the one who is is in blue clothes.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who owns a snake.", "The person who is in red clothes also owns a snake.", "Elena is in pink clothes.", "George is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is is in red clothes lives 2 doors away from the one who is is in green clothes.", "The person who is owns a snake lives next door from the one who is owns a dog.", "Peter is in red clothes.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who is in blue clothes.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is in green clothes.", "Ivan isn't the person who owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 5 also is in pink clothes.", "Ivan isn't the person who is in blue clothes."], "question": "Who owns a hamster?", "answer_options": ["Peter", "Ivan", "George", "Theodora", "Elena"], "answer": "Ivan", "seed": 1729293784267}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a snake or owns a hamster or owns a cat or owns a dog or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in pink clothes or is in blue clothes or is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Ivan, George, Theodora, Elena, Peter.", "The person who is owns a hamster lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a zebra.", "Ivan lives next door from Theodora.", "Theodora isn't the person who owns a zebra.", "Theodora is in red clothes.", "Elena is at house 2.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who is in green clothes.", "The person who is is in red clothes lives 2 doors away from the one who is is in green clothes.", "The person who is owns a cat lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a zebra."], "question": "Who is at house 5?", "answer_options": ["Ivan", "George", "Theodora", "Elena", "Peter"], "answer": "Theodora", "seed": 1729293786237}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a dog or owns a hamster or owns a snake or owns a cat or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in pink clothes or is in red clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Peter, Elena, Ivan, George, Theodora.", "Theodora isn't the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is in pink clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 1 also is in pink clothes.", "Theodora is in green clothes.", "Elena lives next door from George.", "George owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who is in blue clothes.", "George isn't the person who is in blue clothes.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is at house 5 also owns a cat.", "The person who is owns a dog lives next door from the one who is owns a snake.", "Elena isn't the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is owns a dog lives next door from the one who is owns a zebra."], "question": "What pet does the person who is the criminal own?", "answer_options": ["owns a dog", "owns a hamster", "owns a snake", "owns a cat", "owns a zebra"], "answer": "owns a cat", "seed": 1729293788540}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a dog or owns a hamster or owns a snake or owns a cat.", "Any person either is in green clothes or is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in blue clothes or is in pink clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "People's names are George, Elena, Peter, Theodora, Ivan.", "Elena is at house 2.", "Ivan isn't the person who owns a hamster.", "Ivan isn't the person who is in blue clothes.", "Ivan isn't the person who is in green clothes.", "Theodora owns a snake.", "The person who is owns a zebra lives next door from the one who is owns a dog.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who owns a snake.", "Elena is in red clothes.", "The person who is owns a zebra lives next door from the one who is owns a snake.", "The person who is is in green clothes lives next door from the one who is is in blue clothes.", "The person who is at house 5 also is in yellow clothes."], "question": "Who owns a cat?", "answer_options": ["George", "Elena", "Peter", "Theodora", "Ivan"], "answer": "Ivan", "seed": 1729293792164}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a dog or owns a hamster or owns a cat or owns a zebra or owns a snake.", "Any person either is in pink clothes or is in blue clothes or is in green clothes or is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Peter, Ivan, George, Elena, Theodora.", "Theodora isn't the person who owns a hamster.", "Peter isn't the person who is in green clothes.", "Elena is in red clothes.", "Ivan isn't the person who is in green clothes.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who owns a snake.", "Theodora isn't the person who is in blue clothes.", "Peter isn't the person who is at house 1.", "George isn't the person who is at house 4.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who is in green clothes.", "Ivan isn't the person who is in pink clothes.", "The person who is is in green clothes lives next door from the one who is is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is owns a hamster lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a snake.", "The person who is in pink clothes is not the person who owns a snake.", "Theodora is at house 3.", "Peter is the criminal."], "question": "Which is the house of the person who is in pink clothes?", "answer_options": ["is at house 5", "is at house 1", "is at house 2", "is at house 4", "is at house 3"], "answer": "is at house 5", "seed": 1729293796226}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a hamster or owns a snake or owns a dog or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in green clothes or is in blue clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in red clothes or is in pink clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Ivan, Theodora, Peter, Elena, George.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who owns a snake.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who owns a dog.", "Ivan owns a cat.", "Ivan isn't the person who is in pink clothes.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is at house 1 also is in pink clothes."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who owns a zebra?", "answer_options": ["is in green clothes", "is in blue clothes", "is in yellow clothes", "is in red clothes", "is in pink clothes"], "answer": "is in pink clothes", "seed": 1729293799954}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a dog or owns a cat or owns a snake or owns a zebra or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in pink clothes or is in green clothes or is in blue clothes or is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Ivan, Peter, Theodora, Elena, George.", "The person who is in pink clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 1 also is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 5 is not the person who is in green clothes.", "Theodora isn't the person who is the criminal.", "Theodora is at house 4.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who owns a snake.", "The person who is at house 3 also owns a zebra.", "The person who is is in red clothes lives 2 doors away from the one who is is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is owns a cat lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a snake.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is owns a dog lives next door from the one who is owns a snake."], "question": "What pet does the person who is the criminal own?", "answer_options": ["owns a dog", "owns a cat", "owns a snake", "owns a zebra", "owns a hamster"], "answer": "owns a hamster", "seed": 1729293801775}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a hamster or owns a dog or owns a snake or owns a cat.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in pink clothes or is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Elena, Theodora, Ivan, Peter, George.", "Theodora is in pink clothes.", "The person who is at house 5 also owns a cat.", "Peter isn't the person who owns a cat.", "The person who is is in pink clothes lives 2 doors away from the one who is is in red clothes.", "The person who is at house 3 also is in blue clothes.", "Theodora isn't the person who owns a dog.", "The person who is at house 2 also owns a dog.", "Elena is at house 3.", "The person who is is in pink clothes lives next door from the one who is is in green clothes.", "Peter isn't the person who is in red clothes."], "question": "Who is in yellow clothes?", "answer_options": ["Elena", "Theodora", "Ivan", "Peter", "George"], "answer": "Peter", "seed": 1729293817770}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a snake or owns a cat or owns a hamster or owns a dog.", "Any person either is in pink clothes or is in red clothes or is in blue clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Ivan, Theodora, George, Peter, Elena.", "George lives 2 doors away from Peter.", "The person who is in yellow clothes is not the person who owns a cat.", "George is at house 4.", "The person who is in yellow clothes is not the person who owns a zebra.", "Elena owns a dog.", "The person who is in yellow clothes is not the person who owns a snake.", "Peter is in yellow clothes."], "question": "What pet does the person who is at house 2 own?", "answer_options": ["owns a zebra", "owns a snake", "owns a cat", "owns a hamster", "owns a dog"], "answer": "owns a hamster", "seed": 1729293820112}
{"facts": ["They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Ivan, Peter, Theodora, George, Elena.", "Theodora is at house 1.", "Theodora lives next door from George.", "Peter isn't the person who is at house 3.", "Peter isn't the person who is at house 4."], "question": "Who is at house 5?", "answer_options": ["Ivan", "Peter", "Theodora", "George", "Elena"], "answer": "Peter", "seed": 1729293822149}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a snake or owns a cat or owns a hamster or owns a zebra or owns a dog.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in pink clothes or is in red clothes or is in green clothes or is in yellow clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Theodora, George, Elena, Ivan, Peter.", "Theodora lives 2 doors away from Ivan.", "The person who is in red clothes also owns a hamster.", "The person who is is in red clothes lives next door from the one who is is in green clothes.", "Elena owns a hamster.", "The person who is at house 5 also is in yellow clothes.", "Theodora is at house 1.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who is in red clothes."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of Ivan?", "answer_options": ["is in blue clothes", "is in pink clothes", "is in red clothes", "is in green clothes", "is in yellow clothes"], "answer": "is in green clothes", "seed": 1729293824413}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a snake or owns a cat or owns a hamster or owns a dog or owns a zebra.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who owns a snake.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who owns a dog.", "The person who is at house 5 also owns a cat."], "question": "Which is the house of the person who owns a zebra?", "answer_options": ["is at house 4", "is at house 5", "is at house 2", "is at house 1", "is at house 3"], "answer": "is at house 3", "seed": 1729293827070}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a snake or owns a cat or owns a dog or owns a zebra or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in pink clothes or is in blue clothes or is in green clothes or is in yellow clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Theodora, Ivan, George, Peter, Elena.", "Ivan lives 2 doors away from Elena.", "George isn't the person who is at house 1.", "The person who is owns a dog lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a hamster.", "The person who is in green clothes is not the person who owns a snake.", "Theodora lives 2 doors away from Peter.", "Peter is in green clothes.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who owns a snake.", "Elena is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is in blue clothes also owns a dog.", "The person who is at house 4 also owns a zebra.", "Theodora isn't the person who is at house 3.", "Peter isn't the person who is at house 3.", "Ivan isn't the person who owns a dog."], "question": "Who owns a snake?", "answer_options": ["Theodora", "Ivan", "George", "Peter", "Elena"], "answer": "Theodora", "seed": 1729293828715}
{"facts": ["Any person either is in red clothes or is in green clothes or is in blue clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in pink clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Elena, Ivan, George, Theodora, Peter.", "The person who is is in green clothes lives next door from the one who is is in pink clothes.", "Elena lives 2 doors away from Peter.", "The person who is in yellow clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "George is in blue clothes.", "Ivan is at house 4.", "The person who is at house 5 also is in red clothes.", "The person who is at house 1 also is the criminal."], "question": "Which is the house of Theodora?", "answer_options": ["is at house 5", "is at house 4", "is at house 1", "is at house 2", "is at house 3"], "answer": "is at house 2", "seed": 1729293830773}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a hamster or owns a snake or owns a dog or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in yellow clothes or is in red clothes or is in green clothes or is in pink clothes or is in blue clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Theodora, Ivan, Elena, Peter, George.", "The person who is is in red clothes lives 2 doors away from the one who is is in pink clothes.", "The person who is at house 5 is not the person who is in pink clothes.", "Elena lives next door from George.", "The person who is in yellow clothes is not the person who owns a snake.", "The person who is at house 5 is not the person who is in red clothes.", "Ivan lives 2 doors away from Peter.", "The person who is owns a cat lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a snake.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who owns a cat.", "Peter is in pink clothes.", "Elena isn't the person who is at house 5.", "The person who is at house 4 also owns a snake.", "George is in blue clothes."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of Theodora?", "answer_options": ["is in yellow clothes", "is in red clothes", "is in green clothes", "is in pink clothes", "is in blue clothes"], "answer": "is in yellow clothes", "seed": 1729293833538}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a dog or owns a snake or owns a hamster or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in pink clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in green clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are George, Peter, Theodora, Ivan, Elena.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "Elena isn't the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is in pink clothes also owns a dog.", "Ivan is at house 1.", "George isn't the person who is in red clothes.", "The person who is at house 5 is not the person who is in blue clothes.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who owns a hamster.", "Ivan isn't the person who is the criminal.", "Ivan isn't the person who owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 5 is not the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is the criminal is not the person who owns a dog.", "The person who is owns a cat lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a hamster.", "The person who is at house 2 also owns a snake.", "The person who is at house 2 also is in yellow clothes.", "Theodora isn't the person who is at house 4.", "Peter isn't the person who is in red clothes.", "The person who is at house 4 also is in red clothes."], "question": "Which is the house of the person who is the criminal?", "answer_options": ["is at house 3", "is at house 5", "is at house 2", "is at house 1", "is at house 4"], "answer": "is at house 2", "seed": 1729293838705}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a dog or owns a snake or owns a zebra or owns a cat or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in green clothes or is in blue clothes or is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in pink clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "The person who is at house 2 also owns a snake.", "The person who is at house 1 also is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is owns a dog lives next door from the one who is owns a zebra.", "The person who is at house 3 also owns a hamster."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who owns a cat?", "answer_options": ["is in green clothes", "is in blue clothes", "is in red clothes", "is in yellow clothes", "is in pink clothes"], "answer": "is in yellow clothes", "seed": 1729293843940}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a snake or owns a cat or owns a zebra or owns a hamster or owns a dog.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in pink clothes or is in red clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Elena, Peter, Theodora, Ivan, George.", "Elena isn't the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is the criminal is not the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is at house 1 also is in green clothes.", "Theodora isn't the person who is the criminal.", "Ivan is at house 4.", "Peter owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who is in red clothes.", "The person who is in blue clothes also owns a snake.", "The person who is the criminal is not the person who owns a dog.", "The person who is at house 5 also owns a cat.", "Theodora owns a zebra.", "The person who is at house 5 also is in yellow clothes.", "Elena isn't the person who is at house 1.", "The person who is owns a snake lives next door from the one who is owns a zebra.", "Theodora is in pink clothes."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who is the criminal?", "answer_options": ["is in blue clothes", "is in yellow clothes", "is in pink clothes", "is in red clothes", "is in green clothes"], "answer": "is in yellow clothes", "seed": 1729293845428}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a dog or owns a cat or owns a hamster or owns a snake or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in pink clothes or is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Elena, George, Ivan, Peter, Theodora.", "Peter is at house 5.", "Ivan owns a hamster.", "Elena isn't the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who owns a hamster.", "George lives next door from Ivan.", "The person who is at house 5 is not the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is in pink clothes is not the person who owns a zebra.", "Theodora isn't the person who is at house 1.", "The person who is at house 2 also is in pink clothes.", "Elena lives 2 doors away from Ivan."], "question": "What pet does the person who is at house 4 own?", "answer_options": ["owns a dog", "owns a cat", "owns a hamster", "owns a snake", "owns a zebra"], "answer": "owns a zebra", "seed": 1729293849296}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a zebra or owns a dog or owns a snake or owns a cat.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in blue clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in pink clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Theodora, Elena, Ivan, George, Peter.", "The person who is the criminal is not the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is in red clothes also owns a hamster.", "The person who is at house 5 is not the person who is the criminal.", "Elena isn't the person who is at house 5.", "Theodora owns a hamster.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is is in blue clothes lives 2 doors away from the one who is is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who owns a snake.", "Elena isn't the person who is in yellow clothes.", "Elena isn't the person who is at house 4.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who owns a cat.", "Elena isn't the person who owns a dog.", "The person who is at house 2 also is in red clothes.", "Peter is at house 1."], "question": "Who is the criminal?", "answer_options": ["Theodora", "Elena", "Ivan", "George", "Peter"], "answer": "Peter", "seed": 1729293851772}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a dog or owns a hamster or owns a snake or owns a zebra.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Ivan, Elena, Peter, George, Theodora.", "George is at house 2.", "The person who is at house 5 also owns a dog.", "Ivan isn't the person who owns a dog.", "Peter is at house 3.", "Ivan isn't the person who is at house 1."], "question": "Who is at house 4?", "answer_options": ["Ivan", "Elena", "Peter", "George", "Theodora"], "answer": "Ivan", "seed": 1729293854423}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a dog or owns a snake or owns a zebra or owns a cat.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Ivan, George, Elena, Peter, Theodora.", "Theodora owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 4 also owns a cat.", "Ivan lives 2 doors away from Theodora."], "question": "Who is at house 2?", "answer_options": ["Ivan", "George", "Elena", "Peter", "Theodora"], "answer": "Ivan", "seed": 1729293856140}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a snake or owns a dog or owns a cat or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in yellow clothes or is in green clothes or is in red clothes or is in blue clothes or is in pink clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Peter, Theodora, Elena, George, Ivan.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is owns a cat lives next door from the one who is owns a zebra.", "The person who is at house 5 is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who is the criminal.", "Theodora owns a snake.", "Theodora isn't the person who is the criminal.", "Elena isn't the person who is at house 5.", "Ivan isn't the person who owns a dog.", "The person who is at house 4 also owns a snake.", "Ivan isn't the person who is in blue clothes.", "Theodora lives next door from Ivan.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who owns a zebra.", "Elena is in red clothes.", "Elena isn't the person who owns a cat.", "Ivan isn't the person who is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is in green clothes also owns a snake.", "The person who is in pink clothes is not the person who owns a hamster."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who is the criminal?", "answer_options": ["is in yellow clothes", "is in green clothes", "is in red clothes", "is in blue clothes", "is in pink clothes"], "answer": "is in red clothes", "seed": 1729293858033}
{"facts": ["They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Ivan, Peter, Theodora, Elena, George.", "Peter is at house 4.", "Ivan lives 2 doors away from Elena.", "Ivan lives next door from Theodora."], "question": "Who is at house 2?", "answer_options": ["Ivan", "Peter", "Theodora", "Elena", "George"], "answer": "Theodora", "seed": 1729293860820}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a hamster or owns a dog or owns a cat or owns a snake.", "Any person either is in yellow clothes or is in green clothes or is in pink clothes or is in red clothes or is in blue clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Elena, George, Peter, Ivan, Theodora.", "The person who is in yellow clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "George isn't the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who is the criminal.", "Peter lives 2 doors away from Theodora.", "Theodora isn't the person who is at house 3.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who is the criminal.", "Peter isn't the person who is at house 3.", "George owns a hamster.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who owns a hamster.", "Peter isn't the person who owns a cat.", "Theodora isn't the person who owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 1 also is in yellow clothes."], "question": "What pet does the person who is the criminal own?", "answer_options": ["owns a zebra", "owns a hamster", "owns a dog", "owns a cat", "owns a snake"], "answer": "owns a cat", "seed": 1729293862716}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a snake or owns a hamster or owns a dog or owns a cat.", "Any person either is in yellow clothes or is in green clothes or is in red clothes or is in blue clothes or is in pink clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Peter, Elena, George, Ivan, Theodora.", "Theodora isn't the person who is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is at house 5 is not the person who owns a snake.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who is in pink clothes.", "The person who is is in yellow clothes lives next door from the one who is is in pink clothes.", "Elena owns a snake.", "The person who is in yellow clothes is not the person who owns a snake.", "The person who is at house 5 is not the person who is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who is in yellow clothes.", "Elena isn't the person who is at house 3.", "Elena lives 2 doors away from Theodora."], "question": "What pet does the person who is at house 1 own?", "answer_options": ["owns a zebra", "owns a snake", "owns a hamster", "owns a dog", "owns a cat"], "answer": "owns a snake", "seed": 1729293866817}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a snake or owns a cat or owns a zebra or owns a dog or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in pink clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in blue clothes or is in red clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Peter, Elena, Ivan, Theodora, George.", "The person who is the criminal is not the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is in yellow clothes is not the person who owns a hamster.", "Peter isn't the person who is in red clothes.", "Peter isn't the person who is in yellow clothes.", "Ivan is at house 3.", "The person who is at house 4 also owns a dog.", "The person who is at house 5 also is in pink clothes.", "The person who is is in pink clothes lives 2 doors away from the one who is is in blue clothes.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is in red clothes.", "The person who is the criminal is not the person who owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 5 is not the person who is the criminal.", "Peter owns a snake.", "The person who is at house 1 also owns a hamster."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who is the criminal?", "answer_options": ["is in pink clothes", "is in yellow clothes", "is in blue clothes", "is in red clothes", "is in green clothes"], "answer": "is in green clothes", "seed": 1729293868846}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a snake or owns a hamster or owns a cat or owns a zebra or owns a dog.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in blue clothes or is in pink clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Peter, Ivan, Elena, George, Theodora.", "George isn't the person who is the criminal.", "Elena isn't the person who is at house 5.", "Theodora isn't the person who is the criminal.", "Ivan lives next door from Theodora.", "Theodora isn't the person who is at house 5.", "The person who is at house 5 is not the person who is in blue clothes.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is owns a cat lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a dog.", "The person who is at house 1 also is in pink clothes.", "Ivan is in blue clothes.", "Peter isn't the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is at house 4 also owns a hamster.", "George isn't the person who is in red clothes.", "The person who is the criminal is not the person who owns a snake.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who is in red clothes.", "The person who is owns a hamster lives next door from the one who is owns a zebra.", "The person who is is in yellow clothes lives 2 doors away from the one who is is in green clothes."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who is the criminal?", "answer_options": ["is in red clothes", "is in blue clothes", "is in pink clothes", "is in yellow clothes", "is in green clothes"], "answer": "is in blue clothes", "seed": 1729293877620}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a dog or owns a snake or owns a hamster or owns a cat.", "Any person either is in green clothes or is in red clothes or is in blue clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in pink clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "People's names are George, Peter, Ivan, Elena, Theodora.", "The person who is in blue clothes also owns a snake.", "George isn't the person who is at house 2.", "Peter lives 2 doors away from Theodora.", "Ivan is at house 5.", "Peter is at house 1.", "The person who is is in green clothes lives next door from the one who is is in blue clothes.", "The person who is at house 2 also is in yellow clothes.", "George isn't the person who owns a snake."], "question": "Who is in green clothes?", "answer_options": ["George", "Peter", "Ivan", "Elena", "Theodora"], "answer": "George", "seed": 1729293887353}
{"facts": ["Any person either is in yellow clothes or is in red clothes or is in green clothes or is in pink clothes or is in blue clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Ivan, Theodora, Peter, Elena, George.", "Peter lives next door from Elena.", "Theodora isn't the person who is at house 5.", "Theodora isn't the person who is at house 1.", "George is at house 2.", "The person who is at house 3 also is in red clothes."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of Theodora?", "answer_options": ["is in yellow clothes", "is in red clothes", "is in green clothes", "is in pink clothes", "is in blue clothes"], "answer": "is in red clothes", "seed": 1729293890836}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a dog or owns a snake or owns a zebra or owns a cat or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in pink clothes or is in red clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Ivan, Theodora, Peter, Elena, George.", "George owns a hamster.", "The person who is in pink clothes also owns a zebra.", "The person who is at house 5 also is in pink clothes.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who owns a hamster.", "Theodora is at house 4.", "George isn't the person who is at house 3."], "question": "Who is at house 2?", "answer_options": ["Ivan", "Theodora", "Peter", "Elena", "George"], "answer": "George", "seed": 1729293892361}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a dog or owns a snake or owns a hamster or owns a zebra or owns a cat.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "The person who is at house 2 also owns a dog.", "The person who is at house 5 is not the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is owns a dog lives next door from the one who is owns a snake.", "The person who is at house 1 also owns a cat."], "question": "What pet does the person who is at house 4 own?", "answer_options": ["owns a dog", "owns a snake", "owns a hamster", "owns a zebra", "owns a cat"], "answer": "owns a hamster", "seed": 1729293894421}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a dog or owns a zebra or owns a cat or owns a snake or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in green clothes or is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in pink clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Ivan, Peter, George, Elena, Theodora.", "The person who is the criminal is not the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is in yellow clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "Peter isn't the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is is in green clothes lives next door from the one who is is in red clothes.", "The person who is in yellow clothes is not the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is is in red clothes lives 2 doors away from the one who is is in pink clothes.", "The person who is in yellow clothes is not the person who owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who owns a snake.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who owns a snake.", "The person who is at house 1 also owns a dog.", "The person who is in pink clothes is not the person who owns a cat.", "Peter is at house 3.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who is in green clothes.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who owns a hamster.", "Ivan is at house 1.", "Ivan is in blue clothes.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who is the criminal."], "question": "Which is the house of the person who is the criminal?", "answer_options": ["is at house 1", "is at house 3", "is at house 2", "is at house 5", "is at house 4"], "answer": "is at house 2", "seed": 1729293896517}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a cat or owns a snake or owns a zebra or owns a dog.", "Any person either is in green clothes or is in pink clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in blue clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Peter, George, Theodora, Ivan, Elena.", "Theodora owns a snake.", "The person who is at house 3 also owns a cat.", "Ivan isn't the person who is in red clothes.", "Ivan isn't the person who is in pink clothes.", "The person who is in yellow clothes also owns a snake.", "The person who is is in pink clothes lives next door from the one who is is in red clothes.", "Peter isn't the person who is in pink clothes.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who is in red clothes.", "The person who is is in green clothes lives next door from the one who is is in red clothes.", "Peter is at house 5.", "The person who is owns a snake lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a dog.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who owns a hamster."], "question": "What pet does Ivan own?", "answer_options": ["owns a hamster", "owns a cat", "owns a snake", "owns a zebra", "owns a dog"], "answer": "owns a zebra", "seed": 1729293903746}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a dog or owns a hamster or owns a snake or owns a zebra or owns a cat.", "Any person either is in green clothes or is in blue clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in pink clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Peter, George, Theodora, Ivan, Elena.", "The person who is at house 5 is not the person who is the criminal.", "Peter owns a dog.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who owns a dog.", "George isn't the person who is at house 3.", "Ivan lives next door from Elena.", "Theodora owns a snake.", "Ivan isn't the person who is the criminal.", "Elena isn't the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is at house 1 also is in blue clothes.", "The person who is at house 2 also is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is the criminal is not the person who owns a cat.", "Elena isn't the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is in yellow clothes also owns a snake."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who is the criminal?", "answer_options": ["is in green clothes", "is in blue clothes", "is in yellow clothes", "is in pink clothes", "is in red clothes"], "answer": "is in blue clothes", "seed": 1729293906320}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a zebra or owns a hamster or owns a dog or owns a snake.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in pink clothes or is in blue clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Peter, Ivan, Theodora, Elena, George.", "Ivan isn't the person who owns a snake.", "Ivan lives next door from Elena.", "George isn't the person who is in pink clothes.", "Peter is at house 5.", "The person who is at house 1 also is in pink clothes.", "Elena isn't the person who is at house 2.", "The person who is at house 2 also owns a snake."], "question": "Which is the house of George?", "answer_options": ["is at house 5", "is at house 3", "is at house 1", "is at house 4", "is at house 2"], "answer": "is at house 2", "seed": 1729293910893}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a hamster or owns a dog or owns a snake or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in green clothes or is in blue clothes or is in pink clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Elena, Peter, Ivan, George, Theodora.", "The person who is owns a snake lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a zebra.", "Ivan is in pink clothes.", "The person who is is in green clothes lives 2 doors away from the one who is is in pink clothes.", "Elena lives next door from Peter.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who owns a snake.", "George isn't the person who owns a dog.", "The person who is owns a cat lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a dog.", "The person who is at house 5 also is in blue clothes.", "Peter isn't the person who owns a dog.", "The person who is at house 1 also owns a zebra.", "Elena lives next door from George.", "Ivan lives next door from George."], "question": "Which is the house of the person who is in yellow clothes?", "answer_options": ["is at house 4", "is at house 5", "is at house 2", "is at house 3", "is at house 1"], "answer": "is at house 3", "seed": 1729293913117}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a snake or owns a hamster or owns a dog or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in red clothes or is in green clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in pink clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Theodora, Elena, Ivan, Peter, George.", "Theodora is in blue clothes.", "The person who is in pink clothes is not the person who owns a snake.", "The person who is at house 4 also owns a hamster.", "Ivan lives next door from Peter.", "The person who is is in blue clothes lives next door from the one who is is in red clothes.", "The person who is is in blue clothes lives next door from the one who is is in pink clothes.", "Elena isn't the person who is in pink clothes.", "The person who is at house 3 also owns a snake.", "The person who is in blue clothes also owns a cat."], "question": "Who is at house 1?", "answer_options": ["Theodora", "Elena", "Ivan", "Peter", "George"], "answer": "George", "seed": 1729293916977}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a snake or owns a cat or owns a dog or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in green clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in pink clothes or is in blue clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Peter, Theodora, Ivan, Elena, George.", "Elena isn't the person who is the criminal.", "George isn't the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is in yellow clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is in green clothes also owns a snake.", "Elena isn't the person who is at house 5.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is is in green clothes lives next door from the one who is is in blue clothes.", "The person who is is in green clothes lives next door from the one who is is in pink clothes.", "Elena isn't the person who is at house 4.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who is in yellow clothes.", "Elena isn't the person who is in green clothes.", "George is at house 1.", "The person who is at house 2 also is in green clothes."], "question": "What pet does the person who is the criminal own?", "answer_options": ["owns a hamster", "owns a snake", "owns a cat", "owns a dog", "owns a zebra"], "answer": "owns a snake", "seed": 1729293919658}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a snake or owns a hamster or owns a cat or owns a zebra or owns a dog.", "Any person either is in green clothes or is in pink clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in blue clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "People's names are George, Theodora, Ivan, Peter, Elena.", "The person who is owns a hamster lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a dog.", "The person who is at house 4 also is in red clothes.", "The person who is at house 3 also owns a cat.", "Theodora owns a hamster.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who owns a snake.", "The person who is is in yellow clothes lives next door from the one who is is in red clothes.", "George lives next door from Elena.", "Ivan is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is owns a hamster lives next door from the one who is owns a zebra."], "question": "Who is at house 1?", "answer_options": ["George", "Theodora", "Ivan", "Peter", "Elena"], "answer": "Peter", "seed": 1729293923495}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a snake or owns a cat or owns a hamster or owns a zebra or owns a dog.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in pink clothes or is in blue clothes or is in green clothes or is in yellow clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are George, Elena, Theodora, Peter, Ivan.", "The person who is the criminal is not the person who owns a dog.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is owns a snake lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a zebra.", "Theodora isn't the person who owns a dog.", "The person who is at house 2 also owns a zebra.", "George isn't the person who is at house 5.", "The person who is in green clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "Peter isn't the person who is at house 4.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who is in yellow clothes.", "Peter lives next door from Ivan.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is in red clothes.", "Ivan is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is is in blue clothes lives next door from the one who is is in green clothes.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is the criminal is not the person who owns a cat.", "Theodora isn't the person who is in green clothes.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who owns a cat.", "George lives next door from Elena.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is in pink clothes."], "question": "Who is the criminal?", "answer_options": ["George", "Elena", "Theodora", "Peter", "Ivan"], "answer": "George", "seed": 1729293928773}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a hamster or owns a dog or owns a snake or owns a cat.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in blue clothes or is in pink clothes or is in green clothes or is in yellow clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Ivan, Elena, Peter, George, Theodora.", "The person who is is in blue clothes lives 2 doors away from the one who is is in pink clothes.", "The person who is at house 2 also is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is at house 3 also owns a dog.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who owns a dog.", "Peter owns a dog."], "question": "Who is in pink clothes?", "answer_options": ["Ivan", "Elena", "Peter", "George", "Theodora"], "answer": "Peter", "seed": 1729293935839}
{"facts": ["Any person either is in green clothes or is in red clothes or is in blue clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in pink clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Ivan, Theodora, Peter, George, Elena.", "The person who is is in green clothes lives next door from the one who is is in pink clothes.", "Peter isn't the person who is in green clothes.", "Peter isn't the person who is in yellow clothes.", "Peter isn't the person who is at house 4.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who is in blue clothes.", "Theodora isn't the person who is in pink clothes.", "The person who is is in green clothes lives next door from the one who is is in blue clothes.", "Peter isn't the person who is in pink clothes.", "Theodora is at house 1.", "Peter isn't the person who is in red clothes."], "question": "Which is the house of the person who is in green clothes?", "answer_options": ["is at house 4", "is at house 1", "is at house 3", "is at house 2", "is at house 5"], "answer": "is at house 4", "seed": 1729293937359}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a zebra or owns a dog or owns a snake or owns a cat.", "Any person either is in pink clothes or is in blue clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in green clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Theodora, Peter, Ivan, George, Elena.", "The person who is in pink clothes also owns a hamster.", "The person who is is in pink clothes lives next door from the one who is is in green clothes.", "George owns a snake.", "George is at house 3.", "Elena isn't the person who owns a dog.", "George isn't the person who is in red clothes.", "Elena isn't the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who owns a dog.", "Ivan lives next door from Elena.", "Ivan lives 2 doors away from George.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who owns a dog.", "Peter owns a zebra."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of Ivan?", "answer_options": ["is in pink clothes", "is in blue clothes", "is in yellow clothes", "is in green clothes", "is in red clothes"], "answer": "is in yellow clothes", "seed": 1729293940048}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a dog or owns a snake or owns a zebra or owns a hamster or owns a cat.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in pink clothes or is in green clothes or is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Ivan, Peter, Theodora, Elena, George.", "The person who is in green clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "George isn't the person who is the criminal.", "Elena isn't the person who is the criminal.", "Theodora owns a zebra.", "Peter isn't the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 3 also is in green clothes.", "Ivan lives 2 doors away from Peter.", "The person who is at house 4 also owns a dog.", "The person who is at house 3 also owns a zebra.", "Ivan isn't the person who is at house 2."], "question": "What pet does the person who is the criminal own?", "answer_options": ["owns a dog", "owns a snake", "owns a zebra", "owns a hamster", "owns a cat"], "answer": "owns a dog", "seed": 1729293943625}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a dog or owns a hamster or owns a snake or owns a zebra or owns a cat.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in blue clothes or is in green clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in pink clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Peter, George, Theodora, Ivan, Elena.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who is in red clothes.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is the criminal is not the person who owns a snake.", "Elena is in pink clothes.", "Peter lives 2 doors away from Theodora.", "The person who is in blue clothes also owns a hamster.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is owns a dog lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a snake.", "George isn't the person who is at house 4.", "Ivan owns a zebra.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is owns a snake lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a cat.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who owns a snake."], "question": "Who is the criminal?", "answer_options": ["Peter", "George", "Theodora", "Ivan", "Elena"], "answer": "Elena", "seed": 1729293953012}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a snake or owns a hamster or owns a cat or owns a dog or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in pink clothes or is in green clothes or is in red clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in blue clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "The person who is in pink clothes is not the person who owns a dog.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who is in pink clothes.", "The person who is is in green clothes lives next door from the one who is is in yellow clothes.", "The person who is in red clothes also owns a cat.", "The person who is in green clothes is not the person who owns a dog.", "The person who is at house 2 also is in green clothes.", "The person who is at house 4 also owns a zebra."], "question": "What pet does the person who is in yellow clothes own?", "answer_options": ["owns a snake", "owns a hamster", "owns a cat", "owns a dog", "owns a zebra"], "answer": "owns a dog", "seed": 1729293957981}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a cat or owns a hamster or owns a dog or owns a snake.", "Any person either is in yellow clothes or is in green clothes or is in blue clothes or is in red clothes or is in pink clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Theodora, George, Ivan, Elena, Peter.", "The person who is in pink clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "George isn't the person who is the criminal.", "Elena isn't the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who owns a dog.", "The person who is is in yellow clothes lives next door from the one who is is in pink clothes.", "Theodora isn't the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 1 also is in pink clothes.", "The person who is in pink clothes also owns a snake.", "George is in green clothes.", "Elena isn't the person who is in blue clothes.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who owns a cat.", "Elena isn't the person who is at house 2.", "The person who is in yellow clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "Theodora owns a zebra.", "Elena isn't the person who is in pink clothes."], "question": "What pet does the person who is the criminal own?", "answer_options": ["owns a zebra", "owns a cat", "owns a hamster", "owns a dog", "owns a snake"], "answer": "owns a hamster", "seed": 1729293959535}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a snake or owns a hamster or owns a dog or owns a zebra or owns a cat.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in green clothes or is in yellow clothes or is in pink clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 5 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Ivan, George, Elena, Peter, Theodora.", "The person who is owns a hamster lives next door from the one who is owns a cat.", "Ivan isn't the person who owns a cat.", "The person who is owns a snake lives next door from the one who is owns a cat.", "George is in green clothes.", "Theodora isn't the person who owns a zebra.", "Elena is at house 1.", "Ivan lives 2 doors away from George.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is at house 4 is not the person who owns a dog.", "Peter is at house 2.", "The person who is at house 3 also is in blue clothes."], "question": "Who owns a hamster?", "answer_options": ["Ivan", "George", "Elena", "Peter", "Theodora"], "answer": "George", "seed": 1729293967135}
